

Yuliya Bugayova

Kyiv, Ukraine

Skype: juliya bugayova Telephone: +38(098) 497 92 53

Email: yulya.bugayova@gmail.com
Portfolio website: juliya-b.github.io/

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/yuliya-bugayova

ABOUT ME

Hi, I'm **Front-end developer**. I have several years of experience in Web development. I am friendly, sociable, studious, responsible and smart person. I like to be engaged in self-education, reading books and articles about web development.

OBJECTIVE

I want to work in a good company with friendly staff, where I would take part in challenging projects that will help me evolve as a specialist, gain more experience as a team player and become a strong front-end developer.

SKILLS

- HTML5 + CSS3: semantic and valid code;
- JavaScript : solid knowledge. Creation of custom scripts using vanilla JS and jQuery. Knowledge of ES6;
- PHP: understanding of basic code;
- MySQL: understanding and creation of simple requests;
- OOP: solid knowledge;
- English: intermediate level.

METHOD AND TOOLS

- Libraries: jQuery;
- Methodologies: BEM, Airbnb JavaScript Style Guide;
- Frameworks: Bootstrap;
- Code and graphics optimisation using minification, sprites and compression tools;
- Cross-browser compatibility (IE9+);
- Graceful degradation + mobile first;
- Responsive web design;
- Libraries jQuery;
- Version Control: GIT.
- Automation: npm, Webpack;
- Preprocessors: SASS(SCSS);
- Task management: Asana;
- Graphics editors: Adobe Photoshop CC;

EXPERIENCE

Front-end developer

April 2017 – Now

CF.digital

- Web layouts creation using HTML5, CSS3;
- Creation and modernization of JavaScript code;
- Development of CMS based websites.
- Bug fixing;

Front-end developer

March 2016 - April 2017

Freelance

- Web layouts creation using HTML5, CSS3;
- Creation and modernization of JavaScript code;
- Development of CMS based websites.

CNC system software developer

September 2013 – November 2014

LLC "UKRSPETSSTALPOSTAVKA"

- Creation of 3D models in Siemens NX environment;
- Development of CNC system software;

EDUCATION

Software engineering

September 2007 – June 2012

Kryviy Rih National University

Master's degree